{
    "SOE":[
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What food vendor isn't located at the SOE/SOSS building?",
        "choices": ["Mr. Bean", "Ya Kun", "Subway"],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How many faculty members does SOE currently have?",
        "choices": ["52", "57", "55"],
        "answer": 1
      },    
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Who is the current Dean of SOSS?",
        "choices": ["Professor Hoon Hian Teck", "Professor Emeritus Roberto S. Mariano", "Professor Chandran Kukathas"],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What major listed below is one not offered in SOSS?",
        "choices": ["Actuarial Science", "Arts and Culture Management", "Psychology"],
        "answer": 0
      }
    ],

    "SCIS":[
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What animal is the mascot for Ellipsis, the student representative body of SCIS?",
        "choices": ["Owl", "Parrot", "Cat"],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How many undergraduate degrees are being offered under SCIS?",
        "choices": ["1", "2", "3"],
        "answer": 2
      },    
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "As of 30 Sep 2021, there are ___ students enrolled in the undergraduate degrees in SCIS.",
        "choices": ["1995", "1996", "1997"],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "SOA":[
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "When was SOA established?",
        "choices": ["2002", "2004", "2001"],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Onalu is a tenant at SOA.",
        "choices": ["True", "False", "I Don't Know :("],
        "answer": 0
      },    
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the size of the pioneer SOA batch?",
        "choices": ["60", "90", "80"],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "SOB":[
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How many business majors are there?",
        "choices": ["8", "5", "6"],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which of the following is the student representative body for SOB?",
        "choices": ["Ellipsis", "Bondue", "Oikos"],
        "answer": 1
      },    
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What does LKC in LKCSB stand for?",
        "choices": ["Lum Kah Chye", "Lay Kun Chee", "Lee Kong Chian"],
        "answer": 2
      }
    ]
  }
